One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The prisoners we suspect are aiding Straw Hat Luffy are as follows...
Prisoner number E 8200,
the pirate, Buggy the Clown...
Prisoner number D 0464,
former Baroque Works agent,
Galdino, alias Mr. 3.
Prisoner number C 9915,
another former agent of Baroque Works,
Bentham, alias Mr. 2 Bon Kurei.
Right now, Straw Hat Luffy and Mr. 2 Bon Kurei are causing an uproar in the N-sector of Level 3.
The Blugori can't restrain them!
It seems the two of them are headed for the stairs to Level 4.
However, we've yet to locate the pirate, Buggy the Clown and Galdino, Mr. 3.
A riot in Level 2,
and intruders running wild throughout the prison...
Things've gotten pretty interesting around here.
Great way to kill some time.
It'll all be over for'em anyway, once they get caught.
What happened to Saldeath?
The Blugori couldn't stop Straw Hat Luffy and Mr. 2, so...
...he's gone to suppress the uproar in Level 2.
Why did nobody report the situation to me before it got this bad?!
You were so focused on Hancock-dono that you ignored the reports, remember?
I ignored the reports, you say?!
Did the guests leave, Warden?
Oh, Sadi-chan.
Salute the Jailer!
We've finished preparing for the hunt...
So, what should we do?
Perfect timing. Is anyone on Level 3?
The Minotaurus...
went there.
I see. But there's a way out of Level 3.
I suppose he won't be able to pursue them.
I'll leave the fracas on Level 2 to Saldeath...
Send all remaining Impel Down staff here to Level 4!
Understood, Sir!
If they manage to escape from the Minotaurus and fall down here...
I'll finish them off personally in Inferno Hell!
They've underestimated this Great Prison, Impel Down!
W-What's with this thing? It sure is fast!
It's the Minotaurus!
The Minotaurus?
A cold-blooded Demon Guard!
A monster that tosses people like trash!
That's what it is!
Jailer Beast Minotaurus
A monster? A Devil Fruit user?
Bon-chan!
That hurt!
That thing's fast!
Straw-chan, watch out!
Tamer's Whip!
I'm... dying...
Gear Second...
Rubber...
Jet...
Bazooka!
You alright, Bon-chan?
I-I thought I was dying...
I saw a field of Okama before my eyes...
You really are strong...
I'm sure that monster is still alive, but he must be hurt.
Huh? What?!
I'm so angry! This is just awful!
My makeup is ruined!
Cosmetics, cosmetics! I need cosmetics!
That, and my toe-shoes, clothes, weapons, and...
booze, tears, and Okama Way!
I wanna get down from here now. I'm thirsty and hungry!
There's no cause for concern, Straw-chan!
Getting from Level 3 to
Level 4 is as easy as throwing up!
Seriously?!
Yep! Too, too easy! So easy! Way too easy!
There it is, Straw-chan.
Just climb the great, big wall over there.
The wall? You mean up there?
That's right.
But don't get so excited that you leap over it.
Right!
Hot hot hot hot HOT!
What's with that wall?
It's as hot as a frying pan!
A frying pan, huh? That's exactly right, Straw-chan!
So, you alright?
Ready, and...
Hot!
See this, Straw-chan? Look down there.
What's with this place?
There's so much hot air and smoke!
It's too hot to stand up!
Right?
However, the place below us is, indeed, where you wanted to go: Level 4, the Inferno Hell!
The Inferno. That's below here?
Indeed. As you said,
Level 4 is a massive frying pan.
A sea of boiling blood and fire wait for you down there.
You can try jumping down there, if you like,
but if you don't take care in landing, you won't escape with just a burn.
Beyond this point, every move forward is risking your life.
Bon-chan,
you said there was someone you wanted to see, right?
I'd like to know who this guy is you're risking your life to see.
People call him a "Miracle Man".
Locked away for a crime he didn't commit, he is known as Iva-san!
The Queen of Kamabakka Queendom on Momoiro Island in the Grand Line!
The great Okama Queen, admired by all Okama in the world!
Okama Queen?
Okama have queens? Awesome!
That's right!
I want to meet him!
And if I can, I'd like to save him!
Hey wait! We were in such a nice mood here, and you go and bring THAT thing back here?!
I thought you were trying to escape!
STRAW HAT!
So you wanna come along after all?
As if anyone'd wanna go to Hell!
We were just hiding, and this thing just came flying at us!
I dunno why, though...
Oh, I sent him flying at you.
Oh, so it was you then? WAIT JUST A MINUTE?!
I've had enough of this...
I'd rather just get caught...
Minotaurus, you... damn monster...
My life's at stake here...
I've got no choice but to reveal my trump card!
Hey, Straw Hat!
You remember my super-powerful weapon,
that I used to strike fear into your heart, my Special Buggy-ball?
Nah.
Well...What? Uh...
I had this really powerful cannonball called the Buggy-ball, you see...
It was like, my favorite weapon and stuff...
The Buggy-ball...
If you gave it your own name,
that must mean that you have a lot of faith in this Buggy-ball of yours, right?
Exactly!
And I've made a new weapon that lets me store a mini-version with the same power in my own body!
The "Muggy-Ball"!
You changed the name?!
Take this!
Special Muggy-Ball!
Awesome!
It worked!
Well, that's how it works.
How's that? Remembered it yet, Straw Hat?
Crap! It's still conscious?!
Let's do it, Straw-chan!
Hey, Three! You really can't use your Candle powers here?
It'll melt in just three seconds!
Then I'll have to do it in three seconds.
Flying, I'm flying! My flying Okama Kenpo!
Memoir of that Winter-Sky!
Here I go, Straw Hat!
Candle Lock!
Right!
Rubber...
Hammer Rifle!
We did it!
We beat a monster from hell!
Right! Now let's get going down to Level 4!
This is Level 4.
All our forces have assembled here except Warden Magellan.
Stay away,
Luffy...!
How much time is left before his execution?
29 hours.
Tomorrow at 15:00, this will all be over.
Of course, that's assuming nothing goes wrong.
We'll transfer Portgas D. Ace tomorrow morning.
Luffy...
As long as you are alright, I...
Vice-Admiral Momonga!
What is it?
Red Hair has apparently gotten involved in a fight in the New World!
Red Hair?
Are you sure about that?
Why now?
Against who?
Well... the Yonkou Kaidou!
Kaidou?!
According to HQ, Kaidou said he was gonna take down Whitebeard, and Red Hair stopped him.
However, it wasn't a very large battle...
That sort of thing was bound to happen!
My, how uneasy this sea has become.
With all that's going on now, we can't deal with fights between the Yonkou!
It's possible there's no way to avoid a fight with Whitebeard.
No matter who wins, this battle will be engraved in history.
Hurry, and set sail for Marineford!
Yes, Sir!
Impel Down
Inside the well-hole tower
How many times do I have to explain it, you freaking dumbass?!
Can't you see that pillar of steam?!
Spinning, spinning, spinning-ing-ing!
That's the Inferno Hell down there!
We're not going!
Not to a place like Level 4!
Why?
Whaddaya mean "Why"?!
We're trying to break out!
Break. Out.
We wanna go up!
Up, fool!
Man, what a huge blood booger...
Hey, you listening?!
Just give it up, Straw-chan.
We don't need those spineless wimps.
WHO YOU CALLIN' A BIG-NOSED WIMP?!
What the hell?! How could you possibly mistake what I said for THAT?!
I've decided! I'm going 'round and 'round!
This ain't no joke!
Hey, the ceiling just keeps getting higher and higher...
You're right...
I was just wondering what kind of trick they were using to cause that cracking-sound...
We're the ones falling down!
Dammit! My Muggy-Ball was too powerful, and it caused the floor to crumble!
No, no, it was because my kicks were too fierce!
You're wrong, it was because my punch was too strong!
Oh, no, no... It was because my wax-powers were-
Oh, right, never mind.
It wasn't you, okay?!
We're gonna fall into the fire!
Help us!
“Pool of Blood“
Hey, cut it out!
We'll die!
You're just getting what's coming to you.
How many people have you killed up 'til now?
Do it.
We've had plenty of time to reflect over what we did!
That's right! We're sorry!
Stop it!
IT'S HOT! IT'S SO HOT!
SAVE US!
Carry the logs over there!
No slacking off!
So hot... It feels like my organs are boiling!
This floor is more painful than dying!
I've had enough!
Make way! Move it!
A prisoner is trying to escape!
Hey, move it!
You wanna get thrown into the sea of fire?!
You scum! Prisoners aren't allowed to harm other prisoners!
You wanna get executed right now?!
Code name
Former Baroque Works
Assassin, Daz Bones
What's going on?
Magellan, Hannyabal and all the
Demon Guards are gathered here!
What's gonna happen here on this floor?
Passage connecting level 3 and level 4
It sure is hot down here!
Get your protective clothes on!
If Straw Hat Luffy and the others make it down here, it'll be through this door.
Still no reports?
Perhaps the Minotaurus killed them?
Warden, what're you doing, hiding in there like that?
Hurry up, and come out.
Don't just open it all of a sudden!
It's too bright!
Warden, about that Warden's seat...
When I take over your job, please change it to a less confined one.
Silence. This is the Warden's special seat.
I want to remain in a closed-up area.
I'd rather close my heart to you, too.
If we were gonna wait for this long, it'd have been better to just head...
straight to Level 3.
Now, don't be so impatient, Sadi-chan.
It's not me, I mean these kids.
They can't hold back their bloodthirstiness...
for very long.
Jailer Beast Minokoala (Feasty)
Jailer Beast Minorhinoceros (Quiet)
Jailer Beast Minozebra (Shy)
Reporting in!
It appears that Straw Hat Luffy has entered the Vent Column in Level 3,
though we haven't been able to contact the surveillance.
If so, then he'll save us a lot of trouble if he falls down here.
That's the Pool of Blood beneath him.
Those guys all have Devil Fruit powers,
so if they fall in, they're dead.
Warden Magellan! I have something to report!
The intruder, Straw Hat Luffy, has already reached this floor!
What?!
What do you mean?!
Seems he fell down from the Vent Column.
But the Pool of Blood was right below the hole!
How'd he survive?!
I'm just guessing, but he might have been able to leap to safety from the giant rock that fell down with them.
They got lucky.
Also...
What?
Warden, you stink!
Oh, I messed up.
I mean, this is such a pain!
The Demon Guard, the Minotaurus, seems to have been immobilized and has fallen down with them.
No way?! Did they defeat him?!
Probably.
That can't be! I refuse to believe it!
Calm down!
If they intend to escape from Level 4,
there are only two stairs they can use without security approval.
We will split the forces here into three squads.
Hannyabal, I'll leave the protection of this staircase leading to Level 3 to you.
Sadi-chan, you take the Demon Guards and guard the stairs leading to Level 5.
You're kidding! I don't want to stand guard...
I want to attack them!
There's no meaning to my life if I can't attack them, Warden!
If they come here, I'll just let them escape and push the blame on the Warden...
You got any complaints?
Oh, please stop...
sighing!
Why're you breathing on me too?
My instincts told me that you had evil intentions.
You can do whatever you want once you've captured them.
That's great! I can't wait!
All remaining Jailers, chase after them!
You have permission to kill them!
Yes, Sir!
But please, don't kill them completely!
Don't underestimate me,
Straw Hat Luffy and your gang!
I won't let you have your way any longer!
I will settle this here, in Inferno Hell!
Hot!
What's up with this corridor, it's flashily hot!
Near the "Pool of Blood"
The air is so hot, even my lungs feel hot!
Hurry up! We've gotta hurry and get out of here!
Which way should we go?
You guys are just helpless!
If you clear your mind, the fire is just another Okama.
Not that I don't understand how you feel, though.
This floor is even hotter than the one above us.
It IS kinda hot...
I DO kinda feel like I'm getting roasted here...
HOT!!!
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO CAN'T STAND THE HEAT!
Over there! Let's go!
Where're you going?!
HOT!!!
Be quiet!
Wait... The place Straw-chan is running towards...
Lift
Warden Magellan's Office
Pool of Blood
Staircase Inferno hell
Staircase
Current location
Prisoner's Area
Staff only
Bon-chan's Basics of Level 4
Food and Supplies Storage
Kitchen
The kitchen is over there!
I'm starving too! Straw-chan, wait for me!
Fantastic! If they've got some booze there, it'll be perfect!
Wait, Buggy!
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!!!
Smells nice...
Hot, hot! Smells nice...
We've found him!
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Sure are a lot of 'em!
This floor is way hotter than the one above, but when I get something to eat, I'll feel 100 times better!
Stop him!
Rubber...
Fireworks!
What's the big deal, partner?!
Take a good look.
The enemy are dropping like flies.
Also, Level 4 is known for its screams and torture,
but there's not a single Jailer guarding the fiery torture pits.
Up there! They're up there!
We've got to find out where the exit is while we have the chance!
We might get ambushed and trapped here on this floor!
Ambushed in Level 4?!
But they're after Straw Hat, right?!
It was just an accident that got us here!
Regardless, we've tried to escape, so both our names and faces have been revealed.
I'm afraid that...
there's a high chance that they've gathered
the All-Stars of Impel Down here on this floor, to take care off the riot.
The remaining three Demon Guards are a given...
but if Warden Magellan also shows up, we're done for!
Get out of my way!
Damn... I thought that was a spear or something...
What is that?
Jelly? Poop?
Straw-chan, look up there!
You've been running about freely for far too long!
Who're you?!
M-Magellan!
This is the end for you, persistent vermin!
Editor, Sewil
Timer, Sewil
Quality checker, Grug, Pepperjack